jadootv.com 2015-12-27

# Jadoo TV Privacy Policy | South Asian TV Channels Live

### Introduction

JadooTV Inc. respects your privacy. This Privacy Statement explains what information we collect through our websites (the “Sites”), through our products and when you contact us for support, how we use that information, and what choices you have.

The Sites may contain links to other web sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of any company or individual that JadooTV Inc. does not control, or any web sites that you link to from the Sites. You should carefully review the privacy policies of any web sites that you visit from ours to learn more about their information and privacy practices. The collection and use of your personal information shall be governed by such other party or site’s privacy policy. JadooTV Inc. is not responsible for their privacy practices.

Please take a few moments to read this Privacy Statement. By accessing the Sites or using a JadooTV product, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement and are aware that our policies may change in the future.

### What information we collect

In various places on the Sites and through the JadooTV products, we collect “Personally Identifiable Information” such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, or other information that can be used to identify you or contact you. For example, we collect this information when you create an account, register for our message boards, sign up for our email newsletter, and purchase from our website or register a JadooTV product, download a software update, enter a sweepstakes or participate in surveys, promotions and give-away. From time to time in the future we may offer software updates, upgrades, additional features, services and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information to participate.

We also collect “Anonymous Information” such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, the pages on our Sites that you visit, the search terms that you enter or the advertisements that you click. Anonymous information can and will NOT be associated with Personally Identifiable Information.

Like many Internet sites, we also use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. When you visit our Sites the cookie identifies your computer to us so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit. We also use cookies to measure the traffic to and usage of our site and its different services and features, and other miscellaneous uses.

We also collect the personal information of third parties that is provided by visitors who submit that personal data through our Sites, in connection with, for example, referrals or gift purchases.

JadooTV products upload usage information to JadooTV as part of their normal functioning. The collected information includes the specific identifiers of streams played, duration played, various quality measures, error logs, software version numbers, and other usage statistics. Usage information uploaded from JadooTV products is personally identifiable by product serial number. In some cases, serial numbers are associated with personally identifiable information for customer service and support.

The information collected from many users is aggregated for analysis and, in some instances, made generally available anonymously to users of JadooTV products and JadooTV services. For example, JadooTV may use such information to provide features such as lists of popular videos. JadooTV may also use personally identifiable information to make content recommendations to individual users.

If you do not wish JadooTV to use your information as described in this section, please follow the procedure in “What Choices You Have” below.

We do not intend that children will use the Sites. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age, nor will we accept registration from them.

### How we use the information we collect

We use Personally Identifiable Information that you provided us to perform the services for which the data was collected, such as for order fulfillment, customer support and marketing activities, such as e-mail newsletters and sending you information about products and services that may be of interest to you. Later on in this Privacy Statement, we provide you with more information on how to opt-out of marketing communications.

We use non-Personally Identifiable Information to determine how people use the Sites and its services and to analyze usage and performance of our products and their software and features. For example this data tells us information including how often users click on our advertisements, which files are downloaded most frequently, and which areas of our site are the most popular. Analyzing this data allows us to improve our products and services.

### How we share information

We sometimes use third parties to help with certain aspects of our operations, such as processing credit card payments and providing marketing assistance. When we supply Personally Identifiable Information to these third parties, we require them to use it only for the function they are contracted to perform.

We aggregate the Anonymous Information that we collect and exchange it with advertisers and others who are interested in our services.

We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information as required by law, or if in our judgment it is necessary to protect JadooTV Inc. or our users from loss or liability. We may share some or all of your personal information with our current or future “affiliates” (which means a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control), in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this privacy policy. If we merge with or are acquired by another company, the resulting combined company will use the information you have provided as described in this policy. If we cease operation, your information may be transferred to and used by another company that offers similar or related products or services. While we cannot predict about such an unlikely event, we would hope this could provide you continuity of service.

### What choices you have

If you do not want to receive information about our products and services or do not want to receive information from our partners and others about products and services that might interest you, you can send an email to JadooTV Inc. at privacy@jadootv.com. This e-mail address is being protected from spambots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it . We will keep track of your decision in our database. Even if you choose not to receive information from us, we reserve the right to communicate with you on matters we consider especially important relating to our products or services.

### Postings

If you register to use our bulletin boards, please remember that anything you post is publicly available. Your profile will also be available to other users of our bulletin board service.

### Security

During sessions in which you give us information such as credit card numbers, we encrypt your transmissions using SSL (“Secure Sockets Layer”), and other security technology. This guards against the interception of the information while it is on the Internet. We keep the Personally Identifiable Information you provide on servers that are protected by firewalls and other technological means against intrusion or unauthorized access. They are located in a physically secure facility, and only our employees and agents with a need to know the information are given access. However, there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet. We rely on you to select passwords that cannot be guessed easily and to safeguard those passwords from disclosure. Third parties may unlawfully access transmissions or private communications. Please contact us if you have any information regarding unauthorized use of the Sites.

### Social Network Advertising and Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads (WCA)

The JadooTV and Facebook Web Custom Audience is a specific Interest-Based Ads program that matches people that have shown interest in JadooTV through our website with their Facebook user profile so that we may deliver relevant, interest-based ads on Facebook.com. To find out more about Facebook ads programs, please click [here](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads). You can opt-out of this program and all Interest-based advertising by sending an email to JadooTV Inc. at [privacy@jadootv.com](mailto:privacy@jadootv.com).

### Questions

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or our policies, please contact JadooTV Inc. at [privacy@jadootv.com](mailto:privacy@jadootv.com).
